<textcomponents>
	<component id="ID_title">
		<text><![CDATA[<b>Cisco 1941 Backplane</b>]]></text>
	</component>
	<component id='ID_titleTxt01'>
	<text><![CDATA[]]></text>
</component>
<component id='ID_titleTxt011'>
	<text><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></text>
</component>

<component id='ID_bodyTxt01'>
	<text><![CDATA[<b>Enhanced High-speed WAN Interface Card (eHWIC) slots</b> labeled as eHWIC 0 and eHWIC 1 to provide modularity and flexibility by enabling the router to support different types of interface modules, including serial, digital subscriber line (DSL), switch port, and wireless.
]]></text>
</component>

<component id='ID_titleTxt02'>
	<text><![CDATA[]]></text>
</component>
<component id='ID_titleTxt012'>
	<text><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></text>
</component>

<component id='ID_bodyTxt02'>
	<text><![CDATA[<b>Compact Flash slots</b> labeled as CF0 and CF1 to provide increased storage flash space upgradable to 4 GB compact flash card per slot. By default, CF0 is populated with a 256 MB compact flash card and is the default boot location. 
]]></text>
</component>

<component id='ID_titleTxt03'>
	<text><![CDATA[]]></text>
</component>
<component id='ID_titleTxt013'>
	<text><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></text>
</component>

<component id='ID_bodyTxt03'>
	<text><![CDATA[<b>Console ports</b> for the initial configuration and command-line interface (CLI) management access. Two ports are available; the commonly used regular RJ-45 port and a new USB Type-B (mini-B USB) connector. However, the console can only be accessed by one port at a time.
]]></text>
</component>

<component id='ID_titleTxt04'>
	<text><![CDATA[]]></text>
</component>
<component id='ID_titleTxt014'>
	<text><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></text>
</component>

<component id='ID_bodyTxt04'>
	<text><![CDATA[<b>Auxiliary (AUX)</b> RJ-45 port for remote management access similar to the Console port. Now considered a legacy port as it was used to provide support for dial-up modems.]]></text>
</component>

<component id='ID_titleTxt05'>
	<text><![CDATA[]]></text>
</component>

<component id='ID_titleTxt015'>
	<text><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></text>
</component>

<component id='ID_bodyTxt05'>
	<text><![CDATA[<b>Gigabit Ethernet</b> interfaces labeled as GE0/0 and GE0/1. Typically used to provide LAN access by connecting to switches and users, or to interconnect to another router.]]></text>
</component>

<component id='ID_titleTxt06'>
	<text><![CDATA[]]></text>
</component>

<component id='ID_titleTxt016'>
	<text><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></text>
</component>

<component id='ID_bodyTxt06'>
	<text><![CDATA[<b>USB</b> ports labeled as USB 0 and USB 1 to provide additional storage space similar to flash.]]></text>
</component>

</textcomponents>